够了
Man, that's -- that's enough.
好  没问题
Yeah, man. No problem, man.
闹鬼迷宫
你表现很好  孩子
Did great in there, buddy.
你很勇敢
You were very brave.
宠物乐园
别担心  小家伙  你到家了
Don't worry, li'l dude. You're home, see?
平安无事
Safe and sound.
吃苹果吗
Apples?
走  我们去看看
Come on. Let's go take a look.
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十集
在联邦的第三十天
谢谢
Thank you.
我要女巫帽
I'll take a witch hat.
-选得好  -谢谢
- Good choice. - Thank you.
你是新人吧
You're one of the new people, right?
我听说你们都住在废土  要杀腐尸
I heard you all lived out in the wasteland, killing rotters?
-我猜是吧  -真酷
- Yeah, I guess. - Cool.
所以你应该什么都不怕吧
So, there's probably nothing you're afraid of, huh?
来吧  我带你去有好糖果的地方
Come on, i'll show you where all the good candy's at.
我是梅
And I'm Mei.
朱迪
Jude.
酷名字
Cool name.
你觉得怎么样
So, uh, what do you think?
习惯这一切需要点时间
It takes a minute to get used to all this, you know?
这地方早在我们来之前
You know, this place was up and running
就正常运转了
long before we ever got here.
也许我们不需要做什么来完善它
Maybe we don't have to do anything to make it work.
不  要完善总得做点什么
No, there's always something you got to do to make it work.
还要吗
Want another one?
万圣节快乐
Oh, hello! Happy Halloween!
你一根
And here's one for you...
and one for you.
很好吃吧  喜欢吗
They're delicious, aren't they? You like 'em?
第一名是
And first place goes to...
打扮成我们的墨瑟的
dressed as our very own Mercer...
瑟莱斯特
Celeste!
今年的奖品是
And this year's grand prize is...
十张彩票
10 lottery tickets!
来拍几张照
Let's take some pictures.
感谢大家今天出来
Thank you all for coming out today.
你们看起来都很棒
You all look fantastic,
我很高兴你们来庆祝万圣节
and I'm so happy you're out here for Halloween.
我一直觉得她很优雅
I always thought she was so classy.
我从来不知道她
I never knew anything about her.
我以前常读小报
Mm, I used to read a lot of tabloids.
你们看起来很忙
Hey! You two look busy.
康妮是报刊记者
Connie's reporting for the paper.
我们今天行程排满了
We've got a full day.
工作如何
How's work?
很高兴能再次做报道
"It's nice to be reporting again,
但联邦新闻没有那么
but Commonwealth news isn't exactly...
重磅
...hard-hitting."
你见过帕梅拉了吗
Have you, uh, met Pamela yet?
灾变前  我采访过她一次
"I interviewed her once, before the world fell."
对  你还害她叔叔被赶出了国会
Yeah, and you also got her uncle kicked out of Congress, so...
那是你吗
That was you?
我们得走了
"We gotta go.
化装舞会前我们还有很多事要做
We have a lot to do before the masquerade ball."
过会儿见
See you later.
你应该邀请她去跳舞
You should ask her to dance.
我必须去工作了
I gotta get to work.
晚点见吗
Hey. Catch up later?
嗯  晚点见
Yeah. See ya later.
感谢你照看可可
Thanks for watching Coco.
我今晚来接她
I'll come by tonight to pick her up.
今晚把她交给我吧
You know, why don't I just keep her overnight?
你值完晚班肯定很累
You're sure to be exhausted after the late shift.
你确定吗
You sure?
当然了
Yeah, of course.
好  谢谢
Okay, well, thank you.
我会在圣经研读前来接她
I'll, uh -- I'll get her before your Bible study.
好
Okay.
谢谢  再见
Thank you. Bye.
-住处怎样  有改善吗  -没有
- How's the place? Getting any better? - Hell, no.
这地方简直是纸糊的
No, I think this place is literally made out of paper.
你睡了吗
You sleeping?
没有  一点没睡
Nah. Not at all.
希望基本训练早点结束  换新公寓
Can't wait 'til basic's over and we get new apartments
再次操心钱的事真奇怪
Worrying about money again is so weird.
这只是暂时的
It's not forever.
平等
预备  开始
Ready, set, go!
战况逆转  艾斯拉重整旗鼓
Tide's turning and Ezra's back in the game!
我们还以为要结束了
Just when we thought it was over.
没人知道谁会获胜
There is no telling how this ends!
以西结  来玩嘛
Ezekiel, come play!
我很乐意
Nothing I'd love more,
但我得照顾这些小家伙
but I gotta take care of these little guys.
-我们也是  -好了
- Us too. - Okay.
好了  来感谢以西结
Okay, okay, let's thank Ezekiel
让我们用希瓦的颈圈
for letting us use Shiva's collar, huh?
对你那件戏服来说是锦上添花
It was the cherry on top of that sweet costume, right?
抱歉了  我们必须还回去
Sorry, bud. We gotta give it back.
知道吗  艾斯拉
You know, Ezra...
山顶寨烧毁时  这是你爸爸拿出来的
your dad saved this from Hilltop when it burned
因为他知道这东西对我来说很珍贵
because he knew how precious it was to me.
但还有更珍贵的东西
But there's something actually more precious,
就是你的家人
and that is your family.
所以这条链子归你了  但有两个条件
So this leash is yours, on two conditions.
第一  它要让你和我一样快乐
One, that it always makes you as happy as it made me.
第二  你要怀念希瓦
And two, that you honor Shiva's memory
玩的时候总是要记起它
and always think of her when you play with it.
好好玩吧  孩子
You have fun, buddy.
以西结  你确定吗
Ezekiel, you sure?
嗯  当心就行  那只是条链子
Yeah, just be careful. It's a chain.
有人饿了吗
Who's hungry? Yeah?
看起来他们今天很开心
Looks like they had fun today.
我觉得大家都很开心
Oh, I think it was good for everybody.
是啊
Yeah.
你身体如何
How are you feeling?
也很好
Also good.
借过
Excuse me.
你的医生预约怎么样了
How was your doctor's appointment?
很好  没变化
Fine. No changes.
你有玛姬或莉迪亚的消息吗
Have you heard from Maggie or Lydia?
我相信她们没事的
I'm sure they're okay.
你还好吧
Are you?
在今天这样美好的日子里
On a beautiful day like today?
不能更好了
Never better.
天啊  很抱歉
Oh, gosh. I'm so sorry!
我真毛糙
I'm -- I'm such a klutz!
档案室
卡萝尔
Carol?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
抱歉
Sorry.
打探消息
Snooping.
我很担心以西结
I was worried about Ezekiel.
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?
我知道他要动手术
Well, I know that he needs surgery,
我知道他在排队
and I know that he's in line.
轮到147号要多久
How long before you get to number 147?
太久了
Too long.
病人不知道他们的编号
Patients aren't aware of their place in line,
你能帮我个忙  别说出去吗
so can you do me a favor and keep that yourself?
嗯  当然可以
Mm-hmm. Of course.
以西结知道情况有多糟吗
Does Ezekiel know how bad his chances are?
他知道情况不乐观
He knows the odds aren't good.
但他不知道
But he doesn't know
他几乎没机会动上手术
there's likely no chance he'll get the surgery
除非发生奇迹  他排到前面
unless by some miracle he moves up the line.
对不起  我希望我能做更多事
I'm sorry. I wish I could do more.
欢迎来到杀戳屋
Welcome to the kill house.
在本训练中  杀戮不是首要任务
In this exercise, killing is not your primary goal.
我要的是快速和团队协作
I'm looking for speed and teamwork.
两人一队  两队同时开始
Two teams of two will start the course simultaneously.
一队进入右边的屋子
One team goes through the house on the right,
另一队进入左边的屋子
the other team takes the house on the left.
每队只有一把武器  必须共用
There's one weapon per team that must be shared.
你们的目标是穿过屋子
Your objective -- get through the house
杀光屋内腐尸
and all the rotters inside.
各屋尽头都有一只红色标记的腐尸
There will be a rotter marked in red at the end of each house.
第一支杀掉红尸的队伍
First team to take out their red
离正式入伍就更近了一步
gets one step closer to earning their stripes.
但协作失败的队伍
But fail to work as a unit...
将得到惩罚
see what you get.
哈特  你和托马斯一队
Hart, you're with Thomas.
埃斯皮诺萨  格林一队
Espinosa, Green.
金塔纳  约翰逊一队
Quintana, Johnson.
迪克森  丹尼尔斯一队
Dixon, Daniels.
组队吧
Team up.
我可以和埃斯皮诺萨一队吗
You mind if I go with Espinosa?
我们配合很好
We make a good team.
我问你的意见了吗
Did I ask for your opinion?
埃斯皮诺萨  格林
Espinosa, Green.
迪克森  丹尼尔斯
Dixon, Daniels.
你们先开始
You're up first.
我们可以的  我知道你是最快的
We got this. I know you're the fastest,
而我是最狠的  所以没问题
and I'm the baddest, so we're good.
来吧
Let's do this.
我是杰克
Hey. I'm Jake.
你好  杰克
'Sup, Jake?
我来
I got it!
安全
Clear.
让开
Move.
拿着
Take it!
继续走
Keep going!
救命
Help!
埃斯皮诺萨
Espinosa!
迪克森
Dixon!
那是怎么回事
And what was that?
他没事的  我就在旁边
He was good. I was right there.
我说了  快速和团队协作
I said speed and teamwork.
格林  埃斯皮诺萨  好样的
Green, Espinosa. Nicely done.
迪克森
Dixon.
跟我来
You're with me.
你一定要买这张  可好听了
You have to get this. It's so good.
我没钱
I don't have any money.
你没零用钱吗
Oh. Don't you get an allowance?
你朋友是谁  朱迪
Hey! Who's your friend, Jude?
公主  这是梅
Hi, Princess! This is Mei.
梅是同好啊  我已经喜欢上她了
Oh, I see Mei got the memo. I dig her already.
你们需要帮助吗
You guys need any help?
我准备好结账了
Um, I think I'm ready to check out.
摇滚啊  有品味
Oh, rock on. Good taste.
很高兴与你做生意
Well, pleasure doing business,
欢迎随时回来  女士们
and come back anytime, ladies.
你不用这样做
You didn't have to.
这是礼物  送朋友的
It's a gift. For a friend
收据能给我吗
Can I have the receipt?
不用还钱啦
Oh, don't worry about paying me back.
我想留作纪念  纪念这美好的一天
I'd like it as a reminder. Of a good day.
她要配得上今晚贵客的东西
She wants something worthy of tonight's guests.
这不行
That isn't it.
这么点时间  我们已经尽力了
We did the best we could with the time we had.
她知道你能做到的
She knows you'll come through.
文森蒂美酒
配送地址
俄亥俄州斯普林斯港
林多尔街85号
埃斯皮诺萨  你不用来
Espinosa, we don't need you for this.
我自愿的
I volunteered.
给她一个包  我喜欢志愿者
Give her a bag. I love volunteers.
特别是长这么俏的
Especially ones that look like that.
放这里
Right here.
好  看看圣诞老人给我带来了什么
Alright. Let's see what Santa brought me.
这是在搞笑吗
This supposed to be funny?
他练习时能得到最新武器
He gets the newest ones for his drills.
这叫高级军事训练  墨瑟
Advanced military training, Mercer.
高级军事训练
Advanced military training.
当心点
Hey, careful with that one.
这根牙签吗
This toothpick?
对  不值得我浪费时间
Yeah. It's not worth my time.
你必须顺着甩下去
You gotta swing all the way through.
这玩意儿真可悲  应该挂在墙上
That thing is pathetic. Belongs on a wall.
好了  放腐尸
Alright. Release the rotters.
跟我来
With me.
一次两只  听我命令
Two at a time, on my count.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
你为什么这样做  你...
Why did you do that?! You--
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
这就是联邦未来的士兵吗
This is the future soldier of the Commonwealth?
你不该插手  他不会有事的
You shouldn't have intervened. He would've been fine.
我又没通过团建训练吗
Did I fail another team-building exercise?
你习惯于独自搞定一切  我懂
You're used to handling things on your own. I get that.
但这里的情况不同
But that's not how it works around here.
有时我们得彼此成全
Sometimes we have to set each other up to win.
这和那个小混球的自负有什么关系
What does that have to do with that little prick's ego?
这地方是我见过最好的地方
This place is as good as anything I've seen.
如果你能适应  就能获得体面的生活
It'll give you a decent life if you can cut it.
而我希望你成功
And I want you to succeed.
但你不能自找麻烦
But you gotta get out of your own damn way.
你在外面迷路了吗
You get lost out there?
抱歉  厨房排队的人太多了
Sorry. Long line at the kitchen.
给
Here you go.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
你今天过得如何
How was your day?
-什么  -你今天过得如何
- What? - How was your day?
很好
It was great.
-我交到了新朋友  -是吗
- I made a new friend. - Oh, yeah?
她送了我一张唱片
She got me a record.
你听说过摩托党吗
You ever heard of Motorhead?
那是好东西
That's good stuff.
给  孩子
Here, boy.
不
No. Hi!
-达里尔  -怎么了
- Daryl? - Yeah?
我能有零用钱吗
Can I get an allowance?
可以等到我工作稳定了吗
Can we wait a little while 'til my job settles?
然后我们再说
Then we'll talk about it again?
所以我们能住下
So, we can stay?
你想住下吗
Do you want to stay?
即使在亚历山大清理好了之后
Even after Alexandria is all cleaned up?
-我想住下  -是吗
- I do! - Yeah?
这里很好
It's nice.
只要我妈妈知道来哪里找我们
I think as long as my mom knows where to find us,
我就想住下
I want to stay.
不行  太涩了
Yeah, no. It's way too tight.
告诉马克斯  我们今晚会找到好酒
Tell Max we'll have something by tonight.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
我母亲总是教导我要善于观察
My mother always taught me to be observant.
所以你找到了出去的方法
So, you found a way to get outside the walls, huh?
你想要我做什么
What do you want from me?
我有个朋友在等待动手术
I have a friend who's waiting for surgery,
我要你让他排到最前面
and I need you to get him to the front of the line.
这可是个大人情
That's a big ask.
很难办到
Difficult stuff.
对你来说不难
Not for you.
首先
First things first.
我要确定这酒受欢迎
I need to make sure this wine goes over well.
会受欢迎的
Oh, it will.
我几乎能尝到味儿
I can almost taste it.
真可惜  我的孩子们连芒果都不认识
Shame, my kids don't even know what mango is.
也许他们以后能吃上
Well, maybe they'll have some one day.
我的孩子们
My kids?
近期是不可能了
Not anytime soon.
谢谢
Thank you.
要红酒吗
Want some wine?
我们听说是极品
We hear it's really good.
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Cheers.
怎么了
What's wrong?
这场合不适合我
Not really my scene.
我乐意来到另一边
You know, I was cool being on the other side of this.
但这是你的世界  不是我的
But this -- this is your world, not mine.
好吧  放轻松
Okay. Just take it easy.
既然另一半人这样生活
If this is how the other half lives,
不如好好享受  对吧
might as well enjoy it, right?
谢谢
Thank you.
左边  左边
On your left! On your left!
-看这边  -这边
- Shot over here! - This way!
-幸会  先生  -享受派对
- Good to see you, sir! - Enjoy the party.
-享受派对  -拍一张吧
- Enjoy the party. - Quick photo?
再看这边一眼  先生
One more look. This way, sir.
天啊  他恨你
Wow. He hates you.
那是笑里带恨
That was a hate smile.
墨瑟  墨瑟  墨瑟
Mercer! Mercer! Mercer!
Mercer! Mercer! Mercer! Mercer! Mercer! Mercer!
墨瑟  过来[西语]
Hey, Mercer! Echate pa ca!
你得翻译一下
Gonna need a translation.
我只想打个招呼
I just wanted to say hi.
你今晚很帅  非常帅
You look very handsome tonight. Super guapo.
这不适合我
It's not my thing.
很适合  相信我
Oh, it is. Trust me.
知道吗
You know, uh...
我讨厌这种大活动
I hate these big events.
挺无聊的
Kinda boring.
你想让它变得更有趣吗
You want to make it more interesting?
陪我去吧
Join me?
我会很荣幸的
I would be honored.
姓名
Name?
她是和我一起的
She's with me.
有着装要求的
There's a dress code.
公主
Princess!
帕梅拉  你觉得红酒怎样
Pamela, how do you like the wine?
还行
It's fine.
失陪了  兰斯  我要去接受采访
If you'll excuse me, Lance, I'm due for an interview.
我们要安排一场会议
Oh, and we need to get a meeting on the books
讨论亚历山大的事
about this Alexandria thing.
-我有一些疑问  -我有个提议
- I have questions. - I have a pitch.
你当然有了
I'm sure you do.
康妮  很高兴再次见面
Connie, so lovely to see you again.
凯利  很高兴见到你
Kelly, nice to meet you.
我希望你们喜欢这个盛会
I hope you're enjoying the festivities.
今天真是个大日子
"Such an eventful day.
但正式问一句
But speaking on the record,
这里的每个节日都这么隆重吗
do you celebrate every holiday with such grandeur here?"
传统能在动荡时期提供慰藉和稳定
Traditions provide comfort and structure in uncertain times.
所以是的  我们重视节日
So, yes, we treasure our holidays here.
但万圣节尤其特别
But Halloween is extra special.
你可能还记得我父亲在白宫的时候
You may remember from my father's time in the White House
这是他最爱的节日
that it was his favorite.
他总是很喜欢化装舞会
He always loved a good masquerade ball.
你父亲会怎么看待这里的
"What would your father say about
阶级分化呢
the class divide on display here?"
很幸运你们找到了我们
Well, we're lucky you've found us.
我们感谢和庆祝每一个
We appreciate and celebrate every single person
为我们充满活力的社区做出贡献的人
who contributes to our vibrant community.
实际上  我想向你们介绍一个人
In fact, I want to introduce you to someone.
凯莉是去年的彩票中奖者
Carrie is last year's lottery winner.
这是她第一次参加化装舞会
This is her first masquerade ball!
容我失陪
If you'll excuse me.
打扰了  帕梅拉  我...
Excuse me, Pamela, I'm
不好意思  抱歉
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
弥尔顿女士今晚行程满了
Ms. Milton has a very strict itinerary tonight.
那人看起来好眼熟
That guy looks so familiar.
是呀  我在车厢里揍过他
Yeah, I kicked his ass in the train car.
-是那个士兵吗  -嗯
- That Trooper? - Uh-huh.
他为什么在端食物
Why is he serving food?
测试  测试 女士们先生们
Testing, testing. Ladies and gentlemen,
请大家注意一下好吗
may I have your attention for a moment, please?
今晚  我很荣幸介绍一位
It is my honor tonight to introduce someone
无需介绍的人
who needs no introduction.
我们尊敬的领袖
Our esteemed leader,
联邦总管
the governor of the Commonwealth,
帕梅拉·弥尔顿女士
Ms. Pamela Milton!
感谢各位今晚前来
Thank you all for coming out this evening.
今晚  我很荣幸
Tonight, I have the great pleasure
让各位率先欣赏一样真正特别的东西
of giving you a sneak peek at something truly special.
这是才华横溢的亚历克莎·帕克的作品
This is the work of the brilliant Alexa Park,
她今晚也来到了现场
who is here tonight.
别害羞  亚历克莎
Don't be shy, Alexa.
帕克女士花了九个月用心创作了这幅画
It took Ms. Park nine months to lovingly create this painting.
和我们的众多公民一样
Like many of our citizens,
她在外面受到了严重伤害
she sustained serious injuries out in the world
后来在联邦里得到了庇护
before she found sanctuary at the Commonwealth.
感谢我父亲的牺牲
Thanks to my father's sacrifices,
我们才能在这里
we are all here.
一砖一瓦
Brick by brick and block by block,
将世界重建成以前的样子
we're putting the world back together the way it was.
我父亲一定会很自豪
My father would be so proud
看到联邦今天的样子
to see what the Commonwealth is today.
还有它对所有公民无微不至的保护和关怀
How much this place protects and cares for all its citizens.
胡扯
Bullshit!
这是胡扯
This is bullshit!
-先生  够了  -这里真有人相信
- Sir, that's enough - Does anyone here really believe
联邦关怀所有公民吗
the Commonwealth cares for all its citizens?
你认识我吗
Do you know who I am?
先生  现在不合适
Sir, this isn't the time.
请你停下
Please, you need to stop.
别靠近
Don't come any closer!
别靠近  我只想谈谈
Don't come any closer! I just want to talk.
拜托你和我说句话
Will you please just talk to me?!
我愿为这地方献出生命  我叫什么
I would've died for this place. What's my name?!
我不知道  但我想知道
I don't know. But I'd like to.
泰勒·戴维斯  我曾是个士兵
Tyler Davis. I was a Trooper.
我一直在努力和你说上话
I tried and I tried to reach you.
犯了一次错  我就失去了一切
One mistake and I lost everything.
我来这里是为了和你谈谈  让你倾听
I came here to talk to you, to make you listen.
泰勒  我想听
Tyler. I want to listen.
我们两人可以单独谈谈
Let's talk, just the two of us --
别骗人
Don't lie!
你只在乎这个
This is what you care about.
华丽的派对和绘画
Fancy parties and paintings.
而不是我这样的人
Not people like me.
我们对你来说什么都不是
We're nothing to you.
-可以随意支配  -你错了  泰勒
- Disposable. - You're wrong, Tyler.
我看到你了
I see you.
我明白你很难受  我想改变这点
I see you're hurting and I want to fix that.
但首先  你要保证不伤害别人
But first, you have to promise not to hurt anyone else.
请放下刀  放了我的助理
Please put down the knife and let my assistant go.
她叫麦克斯
Her name is Max.
我和你一样
I'm like you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
麦克斯
Max.
他伤到你了吗
Did he hurt you?
我没事  我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
傻站着干什么
Just gonna stand there?
去追他啊
Go after him!
抓住他
Get him.
南楼和屋顶安全
South wing and roof, all clear.
迪克森在哪
I need a status on Dixon.
无处可逃了
Got nowhere to go.
你要抓走我吗
You taking me in?
我有别的选择吗
You gonna give me a choice?
该死  我不想...
Shit, I didn't mean to...
我只想和她谈谈
I just wanted to talk to her,
让她明白
to get her to understand.
但这永远不可能发生
But that was never gonna happen.
住手
Stop!
别这样做
Don't do that.
我对一名囚犯违反了规定  我被打了
I screwed up protocols with a prisoner. I got beat up.
失去了公寓  消费卡
Lost my apartment, my spending card...
我没法再帮助妹妹和孩子们
I have no way to help my sister or kids.
你有个妹妹
You got a sister.
也就是说你有家人
That means you got family.
我们很多人现在已经没家人了
A lot of us don't get to have that anymore.
别让她失去家人
Don't take that away from her.
这不公平
It's not fair.
转身
Turn around.
走吧
Let's go.
你抓到这混蛋了
You caught the bastard.
终于做对了一件事
Finally did something right.
不
No.
抓到他的是你
No, you caught him.
去吧  带他去见你妈妈
Go ahead. Take him to your mom.
他可能挟持任何人
He could have grabbed anyone.
干得好  塞巴斯蒂安
Well done, Sebastian.
押走
Remove him.
你以为除掉我能解决任何问题吗
You think getting rid of me solves anything?
还有上千个像我一样的人
There are thousands more like me.
反抗联邦
Resist the Commonwealth!
重视工人
Visibility for workers!
人人平等
Equality for all!
真有上千人吗
Are there thousands more?
没有
No.
确保这点
Make sure.
请进去  女士  走吧
Inside, please, miss. Let's go.
酒怎么样
How'd the wine go over?
大受欢迎
Great.
这是很好的第一步
It was a good first step.
下一步是什么
What's next?
很高兴你问了
I'm glad you asked.
墨菲  你守门
Murphy, you're on the door.
卡茨  刘易斯  分开服务员
Katz, Lewis, split the wait staff.
查清他是怎么进来的
Figure out how he gained access.
他有没有内应  我要答案
Did he have help? I want answers.
埃斯皮诺萨
Espinosa.
你当服务员的那个朋友
Your friend on the wait staff.
-嗯  -问问她是否知道什么
- Yeah. - See if she knows anything.
遵命
Yes, sir.
你和他共事久吗
So, did you work with him long?
不  我们甚至没见过
No, we never even met.
真的吗  这里的服务员可不多
Oh, really? It's such a small crew here.
你认为我在说谎
You think I'm lying?
我只想查清楚是怎么回事
I'm just trying to figure out what happened.
我觉得挺清楚的
I think it's pretty clear.
你没听见他说的话吗
Didn't you hear what he said?
嗯  他说还有其他人
Yeah, that there were others.
你觉得他是什么意思
What do you think he meant by that?
不知道
No idea.
不过我相信他
But for what it's worth, I believe him.
这地方就像过去的城市
This place is like a city from before.
你记得的
You remember.
我是记得
Yeah, I do.
但你还在这样做
But you're doing this.
你不知道他怎么进来的吗
So, you don't know how he got in?
不知道
Nope.
很好
Great.
没想到是你
I wasn't expecting you.
也很高兴见到你
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
进来吧
Come in.
谢谢
Thanks.
年份佳酿
Vintage?
是的  我可是个贵妇
Yes. I am a lady of high caliber.
最高贵的
The highest.
今天挺热闹吧
Wasn't that something today?
这里人真会办派对  不是吗
They really know how to throw a party around here, don't they?
孩子们很开心
Kids had a blast.
嗯
Yeah.
他还在的话  会很喜欢的
He would've loved it.
嗯
Yeah.
我知道这之前对你来说太痛苦  但是
I know that this was too painful before, but...
这属于你
This belongs to you.
亨利
-你应该留着  -不不不
- You should keep it. - No, no, no.
我想给你
I want you to have it.
这地方可以是个新开始
This place can be a fresh start.
如果你愿意的话
If you want it to be.
你真的还好吗
How are you? Really?
非常好
Just great.
仍然能找到微笑的理由
Still finding reasons to smile.
那么
Well, then...
敬新开始
To fresh starts.
不赖  确实不赖
It's not bad. It's not bad at all.
你总喜欢大杯子
You always took the big glass.
在联邦的第三十三天
你看起来很棒
You look awesome.
谢谢
Thanks.
你看起来很正式
And you look official.
是吗
Yeah? You think so?
我没感觉很正式
I don't feel official.
我给你准备了礼物
Hey, I got you something.
太好了
Yes!
BGM: Motorhead - Eat the Rich
安全
Clear!
-检查周围  -收到
- Check that perimeter.  - Roger that.
反抗  人人平等
重视
工人